我叫Oliver Queen
My name is oliver queen.
经历岛上地狱般的五年后
After five years on a hellish island,
我回来了 心怀一个目标...
I have come home with only one goal...
拯救这座城市
To save my city.
但为此我不能再像以前一样杀戮
But to do so, I can't be the killer I once was.
为了祭奠我的好友
To honor my friend's memory,
我必须重塑自己
I must be someone else.
我必须伪装自身
I must be something else.
"绿箭侠" 前情提要...
Previously on "Arrow"...
尽管我也想让这座城市更安全
As much as I would love to make this city safer,
我的首要使命就是Queen公司
my first obligation is to Queen consolidated
你也一样
And yours is, too.
我读了一些关于英国Lawton的资料
I did some reading up on Lawton.
Lyla 听着...
Lyla, listen...
你是真的认为我查不出
Did you really think I wouldn't find out
他杀了你哥哥?
that he killed your brother?
你以为我不知道你在利用我?
That you were using me?
我死要见尸
I need to see this guy in a bag.
你 还有所有人都该明白
You, of all people, should get that.
这么久
Long time
尤其是对Bratva队长来说
particularly for Bratva captain.
Queen先生
Mr. Queen.
Anatoly Knyazev这个人
Anatoly Knyazev,
对你评价很高
he speaks very highly of you.
应该如此 我救过他的命
He should. I saved his life.
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影子
时间轴: pisces夜
翻译: 西皮jo 伊娃 初见 酱油影
校对: 潇妹纸
这份报告
You were supposed to sign this report
昨晚开董事会的时候就该签了 为何没签?
at last night's board meeting. You know why you didn't?
可能因为我没参加昨晚的董事会
Probably because I didn't attend last night's board meeting.
你去哪了?
Where were you?
我在忙些公司之外的其他事
I have other interests outside of this company.
- 我不相信  - Queen先生...
- I don't.  - Mr. Queen...
你说我们是搭档
I thought you were serious
不是闹着玩的吧
when you said we were partners.
Isabel 我不过没参加一次会议而已
Isabel, I missed one meeting.
是这周一次
This week.
加上上周 就两次会议了
Last week, it was two meetings.
Queen先生
Mr. Queen.
自从我俩接手公司后
Company wide revenue is at double digits
公司收入就一直在两位数
since you and I took over.
- Oliver!  - 干嘛?
- Oliver!  - Yes?
抱歉打断你们...
I'm sorry to interrupt your...
呃!
Grr!
我想和你谈谈
Um, I need to talk to you
你今晚的安排
about your plans for this evening.
和Harper先生的约定
With Mr Harper?
我要失陪了
You'll have to excuse me.
我们还有工作要做
We have work to do.
工作很重要
It's important.
我今晚的计划也很重要
So are my evening plans.
对不起
I'm sorry.
得将计就计了
We are going to have to work on your excuses.
你说得对
You're right.
你太不小心了
You should be more careful.
你都完全暴露了
You're completely exposed.
我知道你在
I knew you were there.
怎么 你想等这些人交易的时候
What, you wanted me to tell you
再让我通知你吗?
when the funny money guys were ready to make a sale?
我们开始吧
Here we go.
不是"我们" 快回家
Not "we." go home.
我有帮手了
I already have help.
这是假币
Here's the fake.
给我们看看真钞
Let's see the real.
右上方有两个人
You got two right above you.
现在只有六个人了
Now they're just six.
待在原地 不许动!
Stay where you are, don't move!
我依法逮捕你 不许动
I want to make a citizen's arrest. Don't move.
好了 我搞定了
That's it. I'm clear.
啊
Aah!
知更鸟 X小队报告
Task Force x to mockingbird.
人已到手 准备归巢
We have the prize, we're coming home.
绿箭侠 第二季第六集
你们是什么人?
Who are you people?
国家安全局? 中央情报局?
NSA? CIA?
我是Amanda Waller
My name is Amanda Waller.
我以为阿格斯的人会更诡秘一些
I thought you ARGUS guys were supposed to be more subtle.
对于我们而言 这已经很诡秘了
For us, this was subtle.
- 我要见Lyla Michaels  - 我也一样
- Then I want to see Lyla Michaels.  - So do I.
Michaels探员已经下落不明了
Agent Michaels has gone dark.
Lyla失踪了?
Lyla's missing?
发生了什么事?
What happened?
她之前去莫斯科追查线索
She was running down a lead in Moscow.
原定两次电话汇报她都错过了
She's missed two of her scheduled call-ins.
那你这是在干吗?
Well, what are you doing about it?
在跟你说话
Speaking to you.
即使我们知道Lyla在俄罗斯的位置
Even if we knew where in Russia Lyla is,
我上司认为派营救小队过去
my superiors believe sending in an extraction team
可能会引发国际问题
could cause an international incident.
在他们看来
As far as they're concerned,
她已经成了照片墙上
she's already a framed picture
相框里的人
on our lobby wall.
为什么你要告诉我这些?
Why are you telling me all this?
因为我知道你和Oliver Queen夜晚的行动
Because I know how you and Oliver Queen spend your nights.
我还知道你的护照是最新的
And I know your passport is up to date.
这样有助于接手Lyla
It would help to start with what Lyla was doing in Moscow
在莫斯科做的事 她追踪的线索是什么?
in the first place. What was this lead she was tracking down?
关于Floyd Lawton下落的一行字
A line on the whereabouts of Floyd Lawton.
是致命一枪
Deadshot.
Lyla为了我才去的俄罗斯
Lyla was in Russia for me,
Michaels探员的位置无人替代
Agent Michaels is an asset I can't easily replace.
我知道对你而言 她同样不可替代
I know you find her similarly irreplaceable.
Diggle先生 把她带回来
Bring her home, Mr Diggle.
谢谢
Thanks.
上次抓你是好久之前的事了
It's been a while since I arrested you.
差点忘了这有多爽
I'd forgotten how good it feels.
我是... 他手下
I was working for... him.
他是谁?
Him who?
那个保护你的人
The guy who cost you your shield.
我是跟着他的 你也是
I'm on his team. You are, too.
还有谁看着比较眼熟?
Anybody else having serious deja vu?
就这样 我们放了他
That's all right, we're letting him go.
我们抓错了
Our mistake.
他在错的时间出现在错的地方
He was just in the wrong place at the wrong time.
好 趁着都还没改变主意
Ok, uh, let's just get out of here
咱赶紧离开这儿吧
before anyone changes their mind.
启动这个机器
The potentially catastrophic risk
潜在的灾难性风险
of turning on this machine
远远超过它可能带来的科学利益
far outweigh any scientific gain that might come from it.
大家需要了解
The people need to understand just how dangerous
这种高科技有多危险
technology like this is.
还有发生灾难性事件的真实可能性
And the very real possibility of a cataclysmic event.
你去哪了? 一切顺利吗?
Where'd you go? Is everything ok?
嗯 需要几天去办私事
Yeah. Just need a few personal days.
- 怎么了?  - 帮一个朋友
- What's going on?  - Have to help a friend.
谁?
Who?
帮Lyla Michaels
Lyla Michaels.
就是他在阿格斯的特工女朋友
It's his spy girlfriend that works for ARGUS.
她为了我去俄罗斯
She went to Russia looking for deadshot,
找致命一枪 现在失踪了
for me. Now she's missing.
Felicity啊...
Felicity...
咱们去参观Queen实业集团
I think it's time we visited our Queen Consolidated
- 在莫斯科的分公司  - 好
- subsidiary in Moscow.  - Yeah.
Oliver 你要干嘛?
Oliver, what are you doing?
帮个朋友而已
Just need to help a friend.
我不能要求你这么做
I can't ask you to do that.
不用要求
You didn't.
Sara啊...
Sara...
我是Ivo
My name's Ivo.
你呢?
What's your name?
我叫Tommy
Tommy.
那么
So.
Tommy 你是怎么到岛上来的?
How did you come to be on this island, Tommy?
我猜不是自己想来的吧
I assume it wasn't by choice.
我 呃...
My, uh...
船在这沉没了
Boat was shipwrecked here.
我是唯一的生还者
And I was the only survivor.
我很遗憾听到这些
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
你仔细探索过这座岛屿吗?
Did you explore the Island much?
探索了一部分
Some of it.
干嘛?
Why?
你之前有没遇到过
You didn't happen to run across
一艘日本海军潜艇?
a Japanese Imperial Navy submarine, did you?
二战期间
During World War II,
每个国家都在研发最先进的武器
Every country was trying to develop the ultimate weapon.
美国有曼哈顿计划
The United States had the Manhattan project, of course;
纳粹有核能计划
the Nazis had Das Uranverein.
还有日本
And the Japanese, well,
他们有Mirakuru计划
they had Mirakuru.
是干细胞治疗和基因治疗研究
Stem cell and genetic therapies,
比其他国家超前几十年
decades ahead of their time.
每一场战争
Every war
都会令科学大业蓬勃发展
advances the cause of science.
日本人就提取出了血清
And the Japanese, they had developed a serum
来增强人体力量
that caused increased strength.
细胞快速再生
Rapid cell regeneration.
- 称之为Mirakuru  - 也就是"奇迹"的意思
- They called it Mirakuru.  - "Miracle."
他们以为自己能建立一个超级战士军团
Thought they could create an army of super soldiers.
他们通过潜艇运送唯一的供给时
They were transporting their only supply via submarine
遭到盟军的沉重火力攻击
when that sub came under heavy fire by the allied forces.
接着在这个岛链上搁浅了
And it ran aground in this chain of islands.
多亏了你...
Thanks to you...
我们现在知道正是这座岛屿
We now know it's this island.
你杀了我朋友
You killed my friends.
也就意味着只能由你...
Which means it's up to you...
来帮我们找到潜艇
to help us find that sub.
你是不是忘了什么?
Are you forgetting something?
你去哪儿?
Where do you think you're going?
塔西提岛
Tahiti.
有意思
That's funny.
飞机旅客名单显示你要去莫斯科
The flight manifest says you're going to Moscow.
我们终点是莫斯科
Well, we're going to stop by there,
先去塔西提岛
you know, after Tahiti.
背着我这个合伙人
What kind of partner decides to interact
和海外子公司联系 你是何居心?
with our overseas holdings behind the other one's back?
一时疏忽 忘了告诉你
It was an oversight.
哦
Oh.
我们的伙伴关系真该庆幸
Well, lucky for our partnership,
我收拾行李超快
I'm a fast packer.
Oliver 她跟着不利于我们解决问题
Oliver, her tagging along does not help matters any.
John 我会看好她
I will take care of her. John.
我们要把Lyla带回来
We're going to bring Lyla back.
不管她身在何处
Wherever she is.
我安排明天早上十点
I've arranged a meeting with the Chief Operating Officer
与莫斯科分公司的首席运营官会面
of our Moscow subsidiary tomorrow at 10:00 a.m.
千万不要缺席
Try your hardest not to miss this one.
我不是你想的那种人
You know, I'm not this person that you seem to think I am.
- 这要看情况  - 看什么情况?
- That depends.  - On what?
要看你是不是利用公司飞机
On if I think you use the corporate Jet
带着助理玩乐一周
for a weekend of fun with your assistant.
什么?
Excuse me?
金发IT女孩突然升职
A blonde IT Girl all of a sudden gets promoted
成为公司首席执行官的助理?
to be assistant to the CEO?
只有两种解释 一个是裙带关系
There are only two ways that happens. One is nepotism,
可她又不像你的表妹
and she doesn't look like your cousin.
那... 是... 绝对不可能的
That... is... absolutely not happening.
那她有什么资格?
What were her qualifications?
除了一堆短裙
Aside from an abundance of short skirts.
她裙子也没有... 那么短
Her skirts aren't that... short.
- 怎么了?  - 没事
- What was that about?  - Nothing.
跟Knyazev都安排妥当了
Everything with Knyazev is set.
你在俄罗斯黑手党也有朋友?
You have friends in the Russian Mafia?
我怎么能不惊讶
Color me at not at all surprised.
你们坐出租车直接去酒店吧
You're going straight to the hotel in a cab.
不是吧 你留下我和她独处?!
No, you're leaving me with her?!
Dig和我要出去喝酒
Dig and I need to get a drink.
额... 我... 也不介意喝一杯
Well... I... wouldn't mind a drink.
Loring女士 没想到你
Ms. Loring. Didn't take you
也泡吧
for the club-hopping type.
我是来做正经事的
Well, I'm here on business.
我妈妈一切还好吧?
Is everything ok with my Mom?
我们得讨论下这个案件
We need to discuss something about this case.
你男朋友Roy昨晚被捕了
Your boyfriend Roy was arrested last night.
我知道 但那其实只是个误会
I know, but it was actually a misunderstanding.
他被释放了
He got released.
有几个记者听到风声
Well, a few reporters got hold of the story
现在他们知道你在和一个臭名昭著的重犯约会
and they now know you're dating a known felon.
Thea啊 你妈妈在受审呢
Thea, your mother is on trial for her life.
她的整个辩护点就是作为一个慈爱的母亲
Her whole defense pivots on being seen as a loving mother
出于本能保护自己的孩子们
who did what she had to do to protect her children
她多伟大啊
What kind of parent she was.
我们得让人们知道 她培养的你能做出正确抉择
We need the people to know that she raised you to make good decisions.
所以如果你在乎你妈妈
So if you care about your mom,
就马上结束这段关系吧
you're going to have to end this relationship immediately.
Oliver Queen? 哈!
Oliver Queen? Ha!
我最爱的美国人!
My favorite American!
欢迎你
Dabro pazhalavat.
好久不见
It has been too long.
John Diggle 这是Anatoly Knyazev先生
John Diggle, this is Anatoly Knyazev.
谢谢接见我们
Thank you for meeting us.
如果Oliver为你打包票的话
If Oliver vouches for you,
你就是我第二最爱的美国人
you're my second favorite American.
先敬一杯
First, a toast.
我不了 谢谢
None for me, thanks.
干杯
Prochnost.
为力量而干杯
To strength.
说正事
Now. Business.
这就是你在找的女人 对吧?
This is woman you look for, yes?
这张照片是两天前拍的 来自古拉格...
Picture is from two days ago, from Gulag...
- 监狱  - Lyla被捕了?
- Prison.  - Lyla was arrested?
也不全是 我听说她想闯入监狱
Not quite. From what I hear, she was trying to break in.
- 为什么?  - 我不知道
- Why?  - I do not know.
但很明显她出不来了
But clearly she had issues breaking back out.
古拉格是俄罗斯最差劲的监狱
Gulag, worst in Russia.
大家叫它地狱
It's called koshmar.
噩梦
The nightmare.
那里聚集了暴力的心理变态狂
It's full of violent psychopaths
和杀手
and killers.
而这不过是守卫而已
And that's just the guards.
Anatoly 我们要想办法进古拉格救她出来
Anatoly, we need a way into the Gulag to extract her.
你进去之后 还没出来就被毙了
You get in, you get shot before you get out.
或者像你朋友那样被囚禁
Or end up like your friend.
所以不可能
Mmm, it's impossible.
唯一不可能的
The only thing that's impossible
就是我们救不出她 空手而归
is us leaving this country without this woman.
我欣赏这家伙
I like this guy.
在俄文里 我们没有"乐观主义者"这个词
We have no word for "optimist" in Russian.
进去地狱的唯一办法
The only way in to koshmar
就是做囚犯
is as prisoner.
那里有个守卫欠我人情
Now, I have guard there, owes me favor.
可能行得通 我会帮你们试试
It could work. I'll give you one shot in twenty.
- 安排一下 我去  - 不行
- Set it up. I'll go.  - No.
必须由我去
It has to be me.
不行
No.
Oliver 如果你在里面出事了怎么办?
Oliver, what if something happens to you in there?
我 Felicity或者Isabel怎么办?
What happens to me, Felicity, or Isabel, for that matter?
你必须在外面行动
You have to be on the outside making the moves.
我进去
I'll go inside.
我能搞定
I've got this.
这毒品可真不少啊
Now that is a lot of drugs.
承蒙Knyazev的好意
Courtesy of Knyazev.
分量足够送我进地狱了
About enough weight to land me in the koshmar.
他们检查你时 你要穿着这个
You need to be wearing this when they process you.
守卫会拿走它 那就如我们所愿了
Guards will take it, but that's the point.
这...
This...
是Knyazev在监狱的线人
is Knyazev's man inside the prison.
一个守卫
A guard.
他知道Lyla被关在哪
He'll know where in the gulag Lyla is being held.
等到处一片混乱时
When all hell breaks loose,
你就要带着Lyla到汇合点与我们碰头 否则...
you need to meet us at the rendezvous point with Lyla, or...
否则我就永远待在俄罗斯了
Or I am a permanent Russian.
我有话直说...
Just thinking out loud...
我们就只能想出这样的方案吗?
but, are we sure this is the best plan we can come up with?
我知道Lyla是你的朋友 但...
I know Lyla's your friend, but...
Felicity Lyla不是我朋友
Felicity, Lyla isn't my friend.
她是我前妻
She was my wife.
你解释下
Explain that sentence.
Lyla和我是在阿富汗军队里认识的
Lyla and I met in the army back in Afghanistan.
但是回到美国就离婚了
But we didn't stay married long once we got stateside.
没有仗要打 婚姻就无法维持了
Couldn't figure out a way to stay married without a war to fight.
后来她加入了阿格斯
So she joined A.R.G.U.S.,
而我就回部队第三次服役
and I circled back for my third tour.
Felicity 我不能把她扔在这不管
I can't leave here without her, Felicity.
不能
Just can't.
还有两分钟
Two minute warning.
祝你好运 John
Good luck, John.
他们抓住他了
They have him.
按计划行事
Clock's running.
进去 进去
Zhivey, zhivey.
快点
Hurry up.
东西没收
Khoroshaya Kurtka.
你犯了什么罪啊?
What, uh, crime fits your punishment?
贩毒 你呢?
Drugs. And you?
我做演讲啊 揭露政府腐败
I gave speech. About government corruption.
哦
Right.
在地狱很少见到你这样的人
It is rare to see one of your people in koshmar.
- 什么 美国人吗?  - 黑人
- What, American?  - Chernokozhiy.
呃...
Ehh...
黑人在这不受欢迎
Chernokozhiy not popular here.
真吓人
Shocker.
你觉得Dig应该没事吧?
You think Dig's ok?
我觉得在你五分钟前问我的时候
I think he's doing the same as he was
他还是老样子
when you asked me five minutes ago.
他们来了
They're coming.
他们廉价卖俄式警车给我们
They sell us Russian police truck for cheap.
这是您需要的车
Vot mashina, kotoraya vam nuzhna.
一百五十万
Sto pyatisot tysyach rubley.
你说什么了?
What'd you say?
请啊
Please.
在俄罗斯有个古拉格
You know, in Russia, there is Gulag.
和这里一样恐怖
Almost as bad as this.
- Sara...  - 别叫出我的名字
- Sara...  - Don't say my name.
如果他们知道我们互相认识 会将我们一起杀掉
If they find out we know each other, they'll kill us both.
我以为你被水淹了
I thought you drowned.
我醒来时 船已经不在了
When I came up, the boat was gone.
我以为你也被水淹了
And I thought you were, too.
我漂了一段时间 直到这艘船...
And I was floating out there for days when this ship...
他们发现我 然后救了我
They found me. And they saved me.
所以你就帮他们吗?
Is that why you're helping them?
我没得选了
I don't have a choice.
我要提醒我的朋友们
I need to warn my friends.
你之前说他们死了
You said they were dead.
他们没那么容易死的
They're not that easy to kill.
别动
Try not to move.
闻起来想吐!
It smells like puke!
它可以治好你的伤口
It'll heal your wounds.
你走吧
You have to go.
离开这
Get out of here.
去高一点的地方
Get to higher ground.
我不会离开你的
I'm not leaving you.
我不想你为了我
I will not be the reason
出事
something happens to you.
那咱们就没什么可说的了
Then we're in agreement.
因为我也做了自己的选择
Because I make my own choices.
你真是一个坚强的女人
You are a strong woman.
为了在乎的人 我什么事都会做
When I care about someone, there's nothing I won't do for them.
这是我们的另一个
Another thing...
共同点
We have in common.
这些烧伤让你的体温不断下降
The burns, they're lowering your body temperature.
这样
Here.
你晚上去哪里了?
Where you been all night?
- 去工作了  - 哦
- Working.  - Oh.
你该好好休息一下了
Well, you deserve a break.
呃 我最近在想
Um, actually, I've been thinking.
我们应该给彼此一点空间
Maybe we should take some space.
我们住在一起 还在一起工作
I mean, we work together and live together.
有点让人喘不过来气
It's kind of getting hard to breathe.
从什么时候开始这么想的?
Since when?
哦 这是不是和前几天来的那个女律师有关?
Oh, wait, does this have to with that lawyer lady dropping by?
不 这只和上个月
No, this has to do with the fact
你被抓进去两次有关
that you've been arrested twice in the last month.
别这样 我已经在努力不惹麻烦
Come on. I've been trying to stay out of trouble.
我都好几个星期没运动运动了
My body hasn't had a scratch on it in weeks.
除了你知道的那次
Well, I mean, excluding the ones that you put there.
那前天晚上怎么回事?
And the other night?
那是个误会
Was a misunderstanding.
Roy啊...
Roy...
这样下去不行 明白吗?
this just isn't working, ok?
我觉得不行
Not for me.
Thea 你不是认真的吧
Thea, you can't mean that.
我是
I do.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
那些人...
Those men...
他们是Vory帮 这里的地头蛇
they are Vory. They are in charge.
最好离他们远点
It's best to stay away.
明白了
Got it.
我要找一个守卫 他叫Sergei Pavelski
Listen, I'm looking for a guard named Sergei Pavelski.
美国佬... 你有麻烦了
American... you are suka now.
确定要这样吗?
Are we seriously going to do this?
没错
Guess so.
这里严禁打架
Fighting strictly prohibited.
你好 我来见Vodki
Vodki, pozhaluysta.
你错过了展览
You missed the tour.
为什么?
What happened to you?
我看到一辆十分喜欢的俄罗斯汽车
I saw a Russian vehicle that I simply had to have.
你来俄罗斯就为了买车?
Is that why you came to Russia? Car shopping?
哦 我只点了一杯
Oh, I just ordered one.
另一杯是我的 再来一杯
One's for me.
这里很冷
This cold room.
关你六个小时的禁闭
Six hours for you.
六个小时? 你不能把我关在这里那么久
Six hours? You can't keep me in here that long.
那就七个小时吧
Now seven hours.
你真是傻得可以...
Well, that was pretty stupid...
这次也一样
then again, you never really were
你又做了一次傻事
one of the brightest guys.
致命一枪?
Deadshot?
你的骨头冻透了吗?
Your spine frozen through yet?
相信我 冷不是问题
Trust me. My problem here isn't with the cold.
你还记恨着我开枪杀了你哥哥?
What, you still haven't forgiven me for shooting your brother?
你可真记仇
Man, you really hold a grudge.
我知道你怎么找来的
I know why you're here.
因为那个阿格斯的女孩
That girl. From A.R.G.U.S.
Lyla找到的不是线索
Lyla didn't find a lead on you.
而直接找到了你
She found you.
你们真的以为
Does everyone really think
- Felicity和我...  - 不
- that Felicity and I are...  - No.
只有Queen实业的员工才那么想
Just everyone who works at Queen Consolidated.
我们是纯洁的友谊关系
She's just a friend.
你看起来可不像和女性只做朋友
You don't seem like the kind of man who has female friends.
我能问你个私人问题吗?
Can I ask you a personal question?
既然我喝了点伏特加 那你就问吧
With some vodka in me, I just might answer.
为什么拯救我的家族企业
Why does saving my family's company
对你来说那么重要?
mean so much to you?
不管雪莉·桑德伯格说得多好听...
Despite what Sheryl Sandberg might say...
Facebook的副总裁
女人想在商界站住脚仍然不那么容易
it still isn't that easy to make it as a woman in business.
我... 牺牲了很多
I've... given up a lot.
所以我如果不力求完美
Which means if I don't succeed at everything,
那些牺牲还有什么用?
then what was the point?
嗯
Hmm.
我能问你一个私人问题吗?
May I ask you a personal question?
你可以试试
Others have tried and failed.
为什么你要绞尽脑汁让我相信你是个大笨蛋?
Why do you try so hard to make me think that you're a lazy idiot?
我知道你不是
I know you're not.
你的那些小花招唬不了我
Underneath that swagger, I see you pretty clearly.
是吗?
Really?
那你说我是什么样的人?
And what do you see?
你很聪明
You're intelligent.
有上进心
Driven.
还很寂寞
And lonely.
你怎么知道的?
How do you see that?
因为我照镜子的时候 看到的也是这样的面容
Because it's what I see when I look in the mirror.
时间紧迫
We don't have much time.
好了
There you go.
我们走
Let's go, let's go.
很高兴见到你 John
Nice seeing you, John.
还需要什么吗?
我觉得还是不要再喝了吧?
你会说俄语
You speak Russian.
只在朋友面前
九岁以前我生活在莫斯科
I was raised in Moscow until I was nine.
然后我被收养了 他们带我来到了美国
And then adopted by a family that took me to America.
过了很长时间我才改掉口音
Took me years to get rid of my accent.
说话像娜塔莎那样 在学校里可交不到朋友
It isn't easy making friends in grade school when you sound like Natasha.
看来你已经寂寞很久了
想知道多久吗?
我... 我等下还有事情
I... don't have a lot of time.
很快的
I'll be quick.
还有五分钟 我们快点
Five minutes. Must hurry.
提醒我事情办完了别忘给你送一大包烟
Remind me to get you a pack of cigarettes when this is all over.
我不抽烟
I don't smoke.
你才不会扔下我自己走了 是吧?
You weren't going to leave without me, were you?
我要杀了你!
I should kill you right now!
不会的
You won't.
- 为什么?  - 因为
- Why?  - Because
只有我知道你的小女朋友在哪
I'm the only one who knows where your little girlfriend is.
你不傻
You're not stupid.
你不会不给自己留好退路的
You wouldn't put yourself in here without an exit strategy.
我带你去找她...
I take you to the girl...
你带我出去
you take me out.
Isabel 我得走了
Isabel, I have to go.
不好意思
Sorry.
你觉得我还用你吻别?
Do I strike you as someone who needs to cuddle?
嗨
Hi.
时间到了 准备好了吗?
It's time. Ready?
嗯 我...
Yeah, I...
你可以让她今天晚上放假 对吧?
I think she can take the night off. Don't you?
- 哦  - Felicity...
- Ohh.  - Felicity...
哦... 在俄罗斯发生的事情就留在俄罗斯吧
It... what happens in Russia stays in Russia.
虽然这么说也没什么意义
Even when it makes no sense whatsoever.
我猜 你想留着它吧
Guessin', uh, you want to hold on to that.
这边走
This way.
你是怎么想的?
What were you thinking?
什么?
What?
俄罗斯有六千四百万成年女性
Over 64 million women over the age of consent
而你和她睡了
in Russia and you sleep with her.
不是说"在俄罗斯发生的事情
So we're not doing the "what happens in Russia
- 就留在俄罗斯"吗?  - 我们还没离开俄罗斯
- Stays in Russia?"  - We're still in Russia.
在这个国家 只要有钱没什么办不到
There is nothing money cannot buy in this country.
Diggle马上就要把Lyla带出来了
Diggle should be heading out Lyla in two minutes.
越狱可不是看起来那么容易
Well, breaking out of prison is harder than it looks.
你们应该知道
You of all people should know that.
别说话
Stay quiet.
跟我走
Follow me.
你要记着回来救我们...
You'll remember the rest of us...
好吗?
Yes?
我答应你
I promise.
一定会回来的
I'll come back.
走吧
Come on.
我们要游出去吗?
Are we making a swim for it?
不 我们一下水就会被乱枪打死
No. They'd shoot us the second we hit the water.
你说过你朋友们有一个
You said your friends, they have one
船上的无线电话 是吧?
of the radios from the ship, right?
嗯
Yeah.
你看起来很专业
You look like you know what you're doing there.
过去这几年我学到了不少本领
In the past year, I've learned a lot of things I never expected to.
我也是
You and me both.
只有听到你的声音 他们才会回答
They won't respond unless they hear your voice.
Shado啊
Shado.
你能听到我吗?
Ni neng ting dao wo ma?
嘿 Slade
Slade.
能听到吗?
Can you hear me?
谢天谢地 你还活着
Thank god you're alive.
没错 我在货船...
Yeah, I'm on the freighter...
Sara 你在做什么?
Sara, what are you doing?
只有两个人
There's only two of them.
他们没有离开迫击炮袭击的地方
They haven't moved from the location of the mortar attack.
这到底是什么情况?
What the hell is going on here?
你刚刚确认了你朋友还活着
You just confirmed that your friends are alive.
这就意味着他们依旧是威胁
Which means they're still a threat.
所以我们还是得杀了他们
You know, until we kill them.
如果我说她就在里面
If I say she's in there,
你为什么不杀了我?
what's keeping you from shooting me?
为了荣誉
Honor.
你也该试试
You should try it some time.
嘿 Lyla!
Lyla!
是Johnny?
Johnny?
准备好回家了吗?
Ready to go home?
你来救我了
You came for me.
无论何时 我都会救你
I always have. Always will.
"致命一枪"在这里
Deadshot's here.
就在监狱里
In the prison.
我知道
I know.
你有什么撤离计划?
What's your extraction plan?
要看情况 几点了?
Depends. What time is it?
我穿着怎么样?
我们走 快 快!
Let's go, go, go, move, move, move!
这边走
This way.
好了
Got it.
我把电话线断了 看守就没法叫增援了
I shut down the phones. The guards can't call for help.
如果你的朋友和救的女人还没来
Your friend and that woman are not here by now,
那就是逃不出来了
they will not be here at all.
好多了
Much better.
全都趴到地上
Oliver 蹲下!
Oliver, get down!
跟我来! 快!
Follow me! Move!
安全了
We're clear.
停车
Stop the truck.
下车
Get out.
下车!
Get out!
往前走
Move.
这就是重视荣誉的坏处 John
That's the thing about honor, John.
你没法自己控制
You can't turn it on and off.
我只是好奇
I'm just curious.
你觉得你哥哥是怎么死的?
How is it you think your brother ended up dead?
你开枪要杀Andy正在保护的客户
You shot a client that Andy was protecting,
结果失手了
and you missed.
我没失手
I don't miss.
你哥哥本来就是我的目标
Your brother was the contract.
谁会想杀Andy?
Who would want to kill Andy?
我不知道具体名字 只有个代号
I don't know the names, just an alias.
叫Hive
Hive.
好好想想 John
Food for thought, John.
好好想想
Food for thought.
我们要不要谈谈昨晚的事?
Are we going to discuss what happened last night?
为什么要谈?
Why would we?
没什么理由
No reason.
明天办公室见
I'll see you in the office tomorrow.
谢谢
Thank you.
你帮了我
You had my back.
现在你也知道有人帮的感觉了
And now you know what it feels like.
你... 你来这里做什么?
Wh... what are you... What are you doing here?
问得好
Good question.
我接到过很多监狱打来的电话
I've gotten a lot of calls from prison,
但从来没接过女友妈妈打来的
but never from my girlfriend's mother.
我突然想到 我从来都没机会
It occurred to me that I've never been given
见见你的这位男朋友
the opportunity to meet the man in your life.
我不知道她告没告诉你
I don't know if she told you,
但你女儿把我甩了
but your daughter kind of dumped me.
那你应该知道 她这么做是为了我
And what you should know is that she did it for me.
Jean跟我说她去见过你了
Jean told me she came to see you.
我跟她说她不该这么做
I told her she shouldn't have.
你为什么不跟我实话实说?
Why didn't you just tell me the truth?
如果我们接着交往...
Us being together...
对她的审判不利
it can hurt her case.
Thea 听着...
Thea...
你的私生活不会成为左右我审判结果的关键因素
your social life is not going to be the determining factor in my trial.
宝贝 你在这一年里经历的事情
Sweetheart, what you've had to endure this last year
比别人两辈子经历的都多
is more than most people go through in two lifetimes.
但你不仅撑过来了 还活得很好
But you've not only survived, you've flourished.
我想很大一部分得归功于Roy
I think a lot of that has to do with Roy.
作为你妈妈 我不允许你不见他
So, as your mother, I forbid you not to see him.
谢谢
Thank you.
我得承认
I have to admit,
我没预料到我的俄国之旅会这样结束
this is not how I anticipated my trip to Russia ending.
我们能活着逃出来可真是幸运
I just feel lucky we made it out of there alive.
谢谢
Thank you.
并不只是谢你救了我
Not just for coming for me.
而是谢你为我做了牺牲
For doing what you had to once you did.
你是说和"致命一枪"合作的事
You mean working with Deadshot.
要知道 我和Carly分手就是因为我做不到爱着她
You know, me and Carly broke up because I couldn't love her
还恨着"致命一枪"
and hate him at the same time.
我很荣幸能成为这例外
I'm honored to be the exception.
Lyla 你永远是例外
Lyla, you're always the exception.
我8点要去阿格斯做任务报告
I have a debrief with A.R.G.U.S. at 0800.
别去了 让Waller操心去
No, no, let Waller stew.
留下来吃早饭
Stay for breakfast.
要是你给我做蓝莓煎饼 我就考虑留下来
Throw in your blueberry pancakes and you may be able to convince me.
你能把这个送到Isabel的办公室吗?
Can you deliver this to Isabel's office, please?
为什么是她?
Why her?
我是说 除了她...
I mean, besides the...
有长腿模特身材这理由之外
obvious leggy model reason.
就这么发生了
It just kind of happened.
这并不意味着什么
It didn't mean anything.
嘿
Hey.
因为我的这种生活...
Because of the life that I lead...
我只是觉得 最好还是不要...
I just think that it's better to not...
和我真正关心的人在一起会比较好
be with someone that I could really care about.
好吧 但我觉得...
Well, I think...
你应该找个比她更好的
I think you deserve better than her.
找到他们的位置了
We have their location.
这个现在对我们没用了
This one's no longer of use to us.
我们来看看你从脑袋里...
Let's see how good you are...
拔子弹的技术有多好
at removing a bullet from your head.
等等!
Wait!
他可能还有用
He could still be useful.
她说得对
She's right.
等我们杀了他的朋友
Once we get rid of his friends,
还需要他带我们去坟墓
we'll need him to lead us to the graves.
我有时候很疑惑 到底谁来发号施令
Sometimes I wonder who gives the orders here.
是你...
You...
还是这个金发小妞
or your little bouzin.
你要回岛上去
You're going back to the island.
叫Oliver对吧
Oliver.
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影子
时间轴: pisces夜
翻译: 西皮jo 伊娃 初见 酱油影
校对: 潇妹纸